<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manuel Tansini</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Manuel Tansini</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 22:14:04 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>/posts/2019/12/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 22:14:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019/12/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description> Kubernetes Objects In Kubernetes, there are a number of objects that are abstractions of your Kubernetes system’s desired state. These objects represent your application, its networking, and disk resources – all of which together form your application. Kubernetes objects can describe:
 Which containerized applications are running on the cluster Application resources Policies that should be applied to the application  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Works</title>
      <link>/works/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2019 11:34:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/works/</guid>
      <description>Positions Held Amazon Account Manager - Kiarenza Funny Dreams s.r.l. [Sportswear,Collectibles, Digital Printing, Garment Printing ITA] Full time - 01/12/2015 - Present - Pescara (PE). Italy
 Planning and content management of Amazon seller channels Monitoring SEO activities on Amazon PPC campaign management on Sponsored Product and Sponsored Brand Monitoring and optimization of day-by-day campaigns on Amazon Analysis of the main search keys for the reference markets Amazon FBA Inventory Management, Shipments and Monitoring  Activities: Management of the flow of daily activities regarding Amazon European Marketplaces (it, de, es, fr, uk) and American (com, ca, mx) within a team of 4 people, Sponsored Product campaigns tracking and maintenance of a maximum ACOS to 20% over a period of two years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 02:42:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description> Hi, I am Manuel Tansini.
I am an Amazon Marketplace Specialist and Tech Nerd Padawan. I love new and exciting projects. Contact me if you think I can help you.
Actually i am based in Pescara, Italy. I have a permanent job as Amazon Account Manager and PPC Architect for local e-commerce agency, I also offer freelance consulting services for companies in Italy and abroad
Book Recommendations  Gene Kim, Jez Humble, Patrick Debois &amp;amp; John Willis: DevOps Handbook Brendan Burns, Joe Beda &amp;amp; Kelsey Hightower: Kubernetes Up &amp;amp; Running Jeff Nickoloff, Stephen Kuenzli: Docker In Action Marijn Haverbeke: Eloquent Javascript  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>